

Sreelakshmi Passavula

Front End Developer

- +46705653999
- ✓ sreelakshmi.passavula@gmail.com
- https://sree0831.github.io/Portfolio/
- Stockholm, Sweden

SUMMARY

Innovative Web Developer with 2 years of experience in website design. Demonstrated talent for UX designs, front and backend web development to optimize online presence. Seasoned expert in languages such as HTML, CSS and as well as scripting languages, Program a server (like using PHP, Python, or Node) Program a database (like using SQL, SQLite, or MongoDB) and JavaScript.

I completed Software Testing Masterclass(2021) from Udemy with core skills PostMan for Restful API testing, JIOS & Android Mobile app testing, JIRA, TestRail, Agile/Scrum and working

as a freelance Junior Software Tester.

As a Front-End Developer, I want to play an important role in the design process by bringing prototypes to life and providing feedback on the designs. In achieving this I am doing industry certified UX design advance courses from Interaction Design Foundation.

EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer 03/2021 - Present

Freelance

- Designed, implemented and maintained WordPress ,HTML,WIX websites .
- Significantly improved page loading speeds for our main client's website.
- Delivered all appointed projects on time.
- Streamlined front end testing practices throughout the team.

Junior QA tester 02/2021 - Present

UTest

- Good working knowledge in all areas of quality assurance including the SDLC
- Follow processes and procedures as set forth in the QA Procedures and supporting knowledge articles
- Experience working on complex projects
- Experience with quality assurance & testing methodologies
- As a Test Analyst with web applications
- Deliver projects on time
- Running Manual and Automated test cases for UI aspects of software
- · Writing detailed test plans for manual and automated test cases

Intern Front End Developer 02/2021 - 05/2021

Voice Her

- Revamped UI and android app interface by using Kotlin
- Developing designs using Figma
- worked with the team in modernizing the front end stack.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Developer 2020

Code Institute, Dublin, Ireland - Diploma in Full Stack Web Developer

Master of software testing

Udemy - QA Tester

Microbiology

SK University - Bachelor of Science

UX Design 2021

Interaction Design Foundation - UX Design

CS50: Introduction To Computer Science 2019

HarvardX - CS50: Introduction To Computer Science

SKILLS

JavaScript Expert UX Advanced React Intermediate TypeScript Advanced HTML GraphQL Advanced Expert CSS Expert Bootstrap Expert SCSS Intermediate Expert Python

Git Advanced MongoDB Advanced

LANGUAGES

English Native Swedish Intermediate